export default data = [
  {
      question: "The main ______ of this test is to find out how much you have learned in high school",
      options: ["countenance","discipline","objective","procedure"],
      correct_option: "objective"
  },
  {
      question: "I hope to live in a student dormitory when I am in college.  I am tired of ______ to school in a crowded bus every day",
      options: ["commuting","dropping","swaying","wandering"],
      correct_option: "commuting"
  },
  {
      question: "They were behind schedule and had to apply for ______ manpower to complete their project in time",
      options: ["basic","extra","introductory","profound"],
      correct_option: "extra"
  },
  {
      question: "Out of ______ and consideration, I always write a thank-you note when someone sends me a gift",
      options: ["concentration","convenience","courtesy","courtship"],
      correct_option: "courtesy"
  },
  {
      question: "The boy ______ to the teacher for his improper behavior",
      options: ["apologized","appealed","approached","attached"],
      correct_option: "apologized"
  },
  {
      question: "The problem with Jane is that she tends to take criticism too ______ and gets angry easily",
      options: ["eventually","positively","intimately","personally"],
      correct_option: "personally"
  },
  {
      question: "Almost everybody is a ______ of many different  Times New Roman ; we show different faces to different people",
      options: ["combination","communication","competition","complication"],
      correct_option: "combination"
  },
  {
      question: "John has been working at the computer for twenty-four hours.  He ______ needs a good rest",
      options: ["accidentally","efficiently","obviously","previously"],
      correct_option: "obviously"
  },
  {
      question: "Nowadays students can ______ information from a variety of sources, such as computers, television, and compact discs",
      options: ["press","express","oppress","access"],
      correct_option: "access"
  },
  {
      question: "Sorry for being late.  Someone gave me ______ directions and I got totally lost",
      options: ["dreary","faulty","handy","steady"],
      correct_option: "faulty"
  },
]
